(The Fun Run will make history...)
(in the running scene.)
(The 1st crew was formed at last.)
(Moomoo, the crew chief with the top initiative)
(Dowoon, the adorable novice runner)
He has a beautiful smile.
(Na Ra, the hot guy with a great smile)
(He always says yes to the crew chief.)
(Ji Hyeon)
(That's how Team Moo Do Ra Ji came about.)
(President Moomoo prepared a present.)
(Is that me?)
(You recognized yourself right away.)
Come on. I'll be honest.
(Sincerely thanking him for the T-shirt)
(What are these under my eyes?)
(You need to get the under eye fat transfer.)
(Chuckling)
(The under eye fat transfer?)
(I already got it done.)
- Let's set out - Let's set out
After the puppy run...
(Moomoo came up with the whale run based on the GPS.)
(Will Moo Do Ra Ji start their run at last?)
(We'll take a taxi.)
(Is this a running tour...)
(or a taxi tour?)
(It was hilarious that they took a taxi.)
(They spent a lot of money on food and taxis. It's hilarious.)
(When will you guys start running?)
(Before our run,)
(we ought to fill up our stomach.)
(Team Moo Do Ra Ji got immersed in the fun part of the run.)
(Munching)
(Their brazenness of having fun didn't stop.)
(Even the foodies had fun watching the Fun Run course.)
(Which way should we go?)
(Shall we go this way?)
(Let's go.)
(The sweet crew chief complied with all of their requests.)
(Team Moo Do Ra Ji was sailing smoothly.)
(Are you all right?)
(Na Ra took care of the crew and the butter.)
(He successfully made real butter.)
(Captivated by the first taste of the Fun Run)
(I love it.)
They're gotten close now.
(I'm so happy to be part of the 1st crew.)
Hyun Moo, which way do we have to go?
We can keep going straight.
- Keep going straight. - Go straight.
We'll complete the head then.
- We're halfway there now. - We'll trace the top of the head.
- Okay. See that rice cake store? - Yes.
We have to turn right at the rice cake store.
We'll complete the head then.
- They're already halfway there. - I bet it's tasty.
- Let's go. - Watch out for your knees.
(Glancing)
Hey, we're going uphill now.
(Spotting)
Gosh, it's quite an uphill.
(They didn't expect the steep incline.)
- It's steep. - We can do this.
We can do this.
Gosh, why is there an uphill?
The GPS doesn't show if there's an incline or not.
(Flustered)
I had no idea that there would be an uphill climb.
Had I known about the elevation,
I would've gotten rid of the head.
I didn't know this course had such a steep incline.
- Seriously. It was very steep. - Yes.
(An unexpected crisis for the Fun Run Crew)
Let's slow down.
- It's quite long too. - That's a long hill.
- The uphill road... - We can do this.
- was about 2km long. - We can do this.
- Right. - Gosh, that's pretty long.
I'm worried about Dowoon.
I'm fine.
(Startled)
- Dowoon. - Yes.
- You're running, right? - I bet you're tired.
No.
You check on me when it gets tough on you.
- You're so mean. - I'm looking after you as a leader.
- Dowoon, are you all right? - Of course.
- Let's go. - Dowoon...
- Dowoon. - Let's keep running, Hyun Moo.
- Are you okay, Dowoon? - Don't use me as an excuse.
I'm not doing that.
- They started... Yes. - They started bickering now.
- They're slightly tired. - See?
People have conflicts when they start to get tired.
The course for the head is tough, isn't it?
- Yes. - Yes.
- This course... - Definitely.
- is an uphill path. - Yes.
Oh, no. We're in trouble.
Dowoon is walking now.
(Dowoon gradually slows down.)
- The forehead... - We're almost there.
- He doesn't look good. - Right.
He shouldn't walk.
(Worried)
When it was around noon, I started to get tired.
I bet.
We kept eating throughout the run.
I kept getting drowsy after the food consumption.
- It was the food and the weather. - He must not have run hard.
He got drowsy from the food while running.
That's understandable.
Oh, no. We're in trouble.
(Moomoo is struggling too.)
This part is the tough one.
I didn't know the Fun Run could be tough.
(I didn't know the Fun Run could be tough.)
- Listen. - Hey. Why look down on them?
I just thought they would be happy from start to finish.
Then it won't be entertaining.
Things get tough for us too.
- It's... - "Things get tough for us too."
There's drama in our run too.
(Singing their crew song to overcome the crisis)
- What? - Doraji
- Moo Do Ra Ji - Moo Do Ra Ji
- I was losing energy. - You guys are losing energy.
We couldn't sing in sync.
- We got this. - We got this.
(Exhausted)
Are we doing this right?
No, listen. A lot of wild animals...
- are sighted in this area. - Wait.
Gosh, you know what?
- That's tough. - It's so steep.
- It was crazy. - The incline...
We should've taken...
- the uphill path earlier. - Right.
Then we would be climbing down here.
- Right? - Yes.
Which way do you want to take?
(At their first forked road...)
(Uphill and flatland)
- We should go this way. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(They chose the flatland right away.)
Had we taken the uphill, we would have run down here.
- You had to run up at least once. - Right.
- Starting with the uphill path... - The uphill like that...
- could have been better. - Right.
The same thought crossed my mind too.
(Why did we choose the flatland earlier?)
It's an uphill.
Uphill.
Never give up.
(Sunken eyes)
I've never seen your dark circles look this bad.
- We can do this. - They're the biggest I've seen.
This is "Dad's Challenge."
It's just like that show.
(Dad...)
Come on.
- It's okay. - Gosh.
- Let's go. - Where are we?
Hey, this is a mountain.
- Why is the head so big? - Gosh.
(Glancing)
- Okay. I'll go in the front. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Go.
- Dowoon. - Dowoon.
- Nice, Dowoon. - Hyun Moo.
- Let's go. - No. Na Ra.
- This is so touching. - Let's go.
- Hyun Moo. - Let's go.
(Na Ra pushes the dad of the group from behind.)
Hyun Moo. Let's go.
No.
All right. Let's go.
Why is there an uphill?
(They run up the hill together.)
The son is pushing the dad from behind.
We're so close. We're almost there.
- We're almost there. - We're almost there.
- We completed the head. - We're here.
(Looking after the tired dad)
- We completed the head. - Let's go.
- Na Ra. - Let's go.
- Na Ra... - Don't abandon your dad.
- Don't abandon him. - You guys make me proud.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(But guys, I'm still here.)
I'll go and get our chief.
I'll go with you.
- I'm making sure you're okay. - Ji Hyeon.
- We're here to get you, Chief. - No.
- We're a team. - Why...
We're a team.
- Why are you taking a break? - Okay.
Why are you taking a break?
(The juniors are encouraging him once again.)
It's not that.
- You should lead us. - Hey. You guys...
- You got it all wrong. - Let's go.
- I was making sure you were okay. - Okay.
I thought there was a tiger.
- Watch out for the plane. - Watch out for the plane.
Watch out for the landing plane.
- We can do this. - Okay.
We got this.
- Let's go, plane! - Let's go, plane!
Let's go, plane!
- We'll start running from there... - Okay.
- to complete the mouth. - Okay.
Okay. It's an uphill. Let's run.
- It's an uphill. Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
Nice teamwork.
- Of course. - This is quite touching.
Yes. You're moved to tears, right?
- Don't overdo it. - There are touching moments.
Right.
- Yes, there are touching moments. - Right, indeed.
- We got this. - Let's go.
(They're close to completing the uphill path.)
We're good.
(Arriving at the top of the uphill path)
- Okay. We did it. - Gosh.
Oh, my. They completed the tough part, the head.
Breathe in some fresh air. Don't run now.
- Okay. - This is nice.
Hey, the vibe here is great.
(That wasn't easy.)
(Looking around)
Are we going that way?
- Chief Moo. - Yes.
- "Chief Moo." - "Chief Moo."
- Are you all right? - Of course.
- Okay. We ran up quite a long path. - Right.
Yes. Seriously.
So...
we started from Saimdang.
We started from Saimdang.
I can't tell just by looking at the pictures.
Look.
This is where we turned earlier.
- Right? - Yes.
The store?
Look.
(The crew chief is lost.)
What?
I only pictured it in my head at home.
I had never been here before.
I was confused.
The paths for the head and the back were fairly simple.
But the paths for the fins and the mouth were complicated.
I was the most concerned about those paths.
I didn't know if we had to go right or left.
I was confused then.
- Do we have to go to the store? - Yes.
We have to go this way.
- Which way? - This way.
(He kindly helps Hyun Moo find the path.)
Where are we?
- Hyun Moo. - Yes?
- I'm a bit dizzy. - Wait.
- We go down and then turn left. - I'm dizzy.
Then let's buy something at the store.
- How about an iced Americano? - Yes.
Okay. There are chairs too.
Let's go in together.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Men ought to drink hovenia tea.
- Men ought to drink hovenia tea. - Right.
(They pick their beverages and go to the counter.)
Hello.
- Do you sell lottery tickets? - Yes.
Lottery tickets? Yes. They should all get one.
- I'll buy one for everyone. - Really?
- If anyone wins, we'll split it. - Okay.
- Don't suddenly go off the grid. - Okay.
How much are four lottery tickets?
- I'll pay. - Twenty dollars?
- No. - No, I'll pay.
- Come on. You should rest. - He already wired the money.
- I already did it. - Let's see.
- You did? - Yes.
- He paid for everything. - Grab one.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Gosh. - We'll split the winnings.
We're going to split it.
- Guys. Listen. - Let's split it.
Don't suddenly go off the grid or disappear.
- Did you check it? - It was a dud for me.
Oh, I didn't check mine.
- Let's check it now. - Let's check.
- Did you check yours? - I did. I didn't win anything.
You check it.
- I didn't take it out since then. - Let's check it.
Na Ra, don't forget that.
We said we'd split the money if anyone won.
- Gosh. - Seriously?
- None of my numbers matched. - Really?
- "None." - "None?"
- None at all. - Same here.
- Check it with the QR code. - Please.
It'd be crazy if he won 2nd or 3rd place.
- Oh, my! - What is it?
- I won 10 dollars. - He got 10 dollars.
- Let's split it. - He won ten dollars.
- He got 3 numbers? - The ticket costs 5 dollars.
- That's pretty good. - Hey.
I guess things will go well for us.
- Team Moo Do Ra Ji has good luck. - Right. It means we have good luck.
- Give me 2.5 dollars later. - Sure.
- Split it with us too. - Yes.
- Sure. - It's 1.42 dollars.
- It's 1.42 dollars. - So 1.42 dollars for everyone?
- It's 1.428 dollars. - If you want it,
- you must run with us. - Gosh.
- You had my moral support. - My heart is racing.
- We're giving you our support. - Yes.
Right.
What about Dowoon?
- Dowoon. Is that why he's not here? - Why...
- Right. - Is that why he's not here?
That must be it.
Is that why he's not here?
I was wondering why he wasn't here.
(Suspecting Dowoon's whereabouts)
He must've won something. We said we'd split it.
- I'm so full. - You're not tired, right?
(He finally gets to take a much-needed break.)
(Refreshed)
- There's a puppy in the back. - That's such a cute puppy.
- Oh, my. You look so adorable. - So cute.
This is crazy.
That puppy was so cute.
I guess it's a neighborhood dog.
Why do you look so cute?
What?
- I see. - It's food for the dog.
Hyun Moo loves animals.
All right. Here.
- How cute. - So cute.
- Look at this cutie. - That's such a cute puppy.
- What a cute puppy. - You're not hungry?
Does my leg look tastier?
(Showing more interested in his leg than the food)
Hyun Moo, this Fun Run is great.
- You can do whatever you want. - You can.
Seriously. You can do everything.
Time doesn't matter for them.
Give it to me.
Here.
I don't think... Wait, will the puppy eat it?
- No. - Yes.
- Go on. - It had to be around the nose.
Look at you. You're eating it.
Oh, my.
That was the happiest and most therapeutic moment.
Is it good?
So we just have to complete the belly part?
Listen. We completed the tail,
the back, the head,
and the fin too.
- The belly is the only thing left. - The belly.
- We're almost done then. - The belly part.
- It's almost over. - Yes.
- It gets harder when we rest. - Let's get going.
Let's start running.
- It was great, sir. - Sure.
- Thank you. - Okay.
- Chief Moo. - Yes.
- Let's get going. - Let's start running.
- Okay. - It's colder when we don't run.
- If you rest too long, - We have to keep running.
- your body will get stiff. - From the end...
We have to decide whether we'll turn left or right.
If we turn left, we'll complete the belly.
- Okay. - If we turn right,
we can also trace the mouth line.
Will it be a mouthless whale...
or a whale with a mouth?
To do that, we have to go back and forth, right?
That will be the mouth.
Then let's turn there.
(Fully motivated)
(They choose to turn right to give the whale a mouth.)
- Hello. - Let's go.
You know what? I love it.
Yes. Look at the view.
(Running while admiring the ocean view)
Hey, our crew song isn't getting us...
- pumped up at all. - Right.
Ji Hyeon, do you know any song that can get our energy up?
Let's see.
- How about this song, Dowoon? - What?
I ran
(Smirking)
That's great.
- I ran - I ran
- For you - I can't watch this.
(The crew chief is excited with the songwriter's permission.)
- Moo Do Ra Ji for you - For you
For you
(We can't leave out our crew name in the team anthem.)
- Moo Do Ra Ji - Moo Do Ra Ji
- My gosh. - Isn't that nice?
I can't keep watching this.
(Their 2nd team anthem pushes them to complete the mouth.)
(While enjoying the run...)
Gosh, that place looks nice.
- How beautiful. - Dowoon. This ocean is crazy
I told you I hated this kind of thing the most.
(But just like he said, there's a crazy view of the ocean.)
- It's so beautiful. - I can't believe this.
Is that the observatory you saw from the ground earlier?
Right. That's the same spot.
(Observatory)
- Gosh, this is insane. - This is crazy.
- This is crazy. - It's incredible.
- It's the charm of the East Sea. - Gosh.
The panoramic view was nothing but the ocean.
- Right. - It was really nice.
I had never seen such a vast ocean like this.
- This is incredible. - Gosh.
- The view here is insane. - It's so beautiful here.
Let's walk around.
- Yes. Sounds good. - We should do that.
(They stop running and will have fun now.)
- That's how the port looked before. - I like the vibe here.
- Gosh. - This is nice indeed.
Hey, it's crazy. They set this place up really well.
No wonder why a lot of zoomers come here.
- Yes. - I see.
(Let me see.)
(What's that?)
- What's this now? - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Four adults.
- Four adults? - Yes.
We have a few activities you can try. Will you try them too?
We have the Sky Cycle and the Giant Slide.
- Gosh. - You can take them to go down?
- Hey, these look fun. - I didn't know about them either.
- Oh, my. - "Sky Cycle?"
I can't do it. It's too scary.
- He was scared of these activities. - I'm scared.
Hold on. I'll talk to my team.
- What's this? - What did you say?
- This looks scary. - No, it doesn't.
We can get on these rides.
There's safety gear.
(A bicycle is suspended 21m high in the sky.)
- You're scared of this? - Yes.
- Why? - I'm scared of it.
The Giant Slide doesn't look dangerous.
- That one's fine. - You think this might be dangerous?
- Yes. - In case the ropes snap?
- Yes. - Has that ever happened before?
No.
(No!)
- "No!" - She got mad at us.
(Flustered)
Just try it. I'm sure we'll be fine.
Everything is tightly secured.
It's all right. All of us will try it.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- I'll charge you for four people. - Four people.
- Let's try the activities here. - Let's go.
(They set out to try the activity.)
I didn't expect us to end up at a fun place like that.
I didn't plan anything down to the details.
All of a sudden, we stumbled across this amazing place.
And that's the perk of the Fun Run.
Stressed runners always...
go on the same predetermined routes like machines.
They would never get to experience this thrill.
Stressed runners?
What are you talking about?
Here's what I noticed...
- about your crew. - Right.
Everyone looks happy, and it looks like a fun run.
But you have an inferiority complex against serious runners.
- Yes, he does. - His inferiority complex...
- is on another level. - He keeps on provoking us.
- I mean... - Why do you keep provoking me?
- Seriously. - We're happy too when we run.
He really went for it.
No. I didn't.
This is it.
- That's the Sky Cycle. - What?
- We can go down after that. - For real?
- I see. - Wait. How can I get on that thing?
- Let me see. - This is it.
You ride the bicycle on a rope.
There's no net underneath?
- There's no net? - No.
- Then... - Oh, no.
- That looks scary! - How can you ride that?
It looks scary.
- That's... - I can't ride that. Oh, no.
Actually, I didn't want to do it either.
I was just as scared of heights as Ji Hyeon.
- I see. - You were?
Hello. Is this a round trip?
- Pardon? - Is this a round trip?
- It's a round trip. - I see.
- Oh, that's even worse. - Yes.
Then why don't we try this, Hyun Moo?
- We're real men. - We'll go first.
Wait here and watch.
- Okay. - The youngest is full of energy.
He stepped up.
- So he's not scared of heights. - He's not.
- There's a locker. - A locker?
- There's been an accident? - Anything that could fall out...
(Shocked)
See? People mishear things when they're scared.
- Everything... - Right.
Can you look down, though?
Of course.
(That's impressive.)
- I'll turn around. - Okay.
I can guarantee this.
I can ride anything except for those vertical drops.
Really?
I just don't want to be dropped.
As long as it's horizontal,
I can even go out of the atmosphere.
This isn't scary at all.
(Peaceful)
Okay.
- You got this, Dowoon. - You got this, Dowoon.
Na Ra, there's nothing underneath.
Exactly. Goodbye.
- Okay. - "Goodbye."
What a nice friend you are.
"Goodbye."
There's nothing under this.
That must be scary for people who are afraid of heights.
- Of course. - Let's go.
Look at the flowers on your way there.
Then look at the ocean on your way back.
(All the preparation is done.)
Going back and forth...
Okay. Let's go, Moo Do Ra Ji.
- Let's go, Moo Do Ra Ji. - Let's go.
- Start pedaling now. - I can just go?
- What? - Go slowly.
- He wasn't scared at all. - Go slowly.
- He's going? - He doesn't get scared.
Start pedaling slowly.
- Good luck. - Go slowly.
- Good luck. - Hey, Dowoon!
(Hyun Moo and Dowoon set out slowly.)
(A dizzying height)
It's pretty high.
- It's high. - This is crazy.
Hey, Dowoon!
(Chuckling)
This is crazy.
This is super scary.
- Super scary. - I can even go out...
of the atmosphere.
- Hey! - How can anyone do that?
Dowoon!
You said you could easily handle any horizontal rides.
I realized I couldn't once I was out there.
Gosh, I hate it.
Look at Dowoon pedaling forward.
(Dowoon quickly goes ahead.)
(Giggling)
How can anyone do that?
(Just watching them gives him goosebumps.)
Look at Dowoon go.
- He's just pushing through. - Dowoon makes it look so easy.
Gosh, this is so scary.
Dowoon is killing it.
That's such a cute smile.
- He's happy... - It's not stopping.
as long as we're not running.
What? Wait.
Chief Moo froze.
(He prefers having fun to running.)
Hey. This is super scary.
Dowoon!
- And that's a long ride. - It is.
- It's longer than I expected. - How can I do this? This is crazy.
I couldn't look down.
- I'm not doing this again. - Look at that.
- Oh, my. - Gosh.
- Look at this. I'm up in the air. - Dowoon.
- There was nothing underneath. - This is crazy. Gosh.
My goodness. It's shaking.
(The two runners are flying over the whale's mouth.)
This is so scary.
(Hyun Moo makes a fuss when Dowoon looks at ease.)
I'm here.
(He passes the turning point as if it's nothing.)
Oh, my.
My goodness.
Goodness. It won't move forward. What do I do then?
- Goodness. It won't move forward. - Why not?
- It was not because of your legs? - I see.
The closer you get to the middle, the looser the rope gets.
Right. It has to go up.
Oh, no.
Dowoon, if this doesn't move forward, I'll have to stay still.
What?
- You must get here first. Hurry. - It's not that.
What were you trying to say?
- I'll go first. - Come on. Wait for me.
My gosh. This is so scary.
How can I...
(Glancing down)
I almost peed my pants.
(Scared)
- Right. You almost did. - Hear me out.
I stopped for a second in the middle.
If you don't pedal, you'll just get stuck in the middle.
- Right. - My gosh.
That's so scary.
This is scary. I don't think Ji Hyeon can do this.
(Staring)
My gosh, this is so scary.
(Getting the chills)
Here I go.
(He sets out after Dowoon as he shakes in fear.)
(Pedaling furiously fast)
- Dowoon got the hang of it. - Dowoon, stop.
- That's fast. - I'm up high.
(Fully enjoying the adrenaline rush)
- Oh, my. Okay. - Come all the way in.
(Finishing the ride in a fun mood)
My gosh.
(He moves along while enjoying the view.)
Wave for us.
(Lifting his hand)
Just for a second.
(Lifting his hands)
- I couldn't do it. - You're playful.
(Moomoo returns safely too.)
Hey, you were so good at this.
Did you look down?
- You'd pee your pants then. - It's scary.
Try it. It's fun.
You just said it was scary.
It's scary on your way there, but it's so fun on your way back.
(The crew chief wants everyone to try this fun activity.)
Try it.
Let's try it.
- You'd be curious, though. - Let me explain.
- Right. - It won't catch you off guard.
- Right. - Try it.
- Ji Hyeon. - Let's just get it over with.
- Okay. - Let's do it.
Just get it over with.
- He'll try it? - Na Ra.
This will be so scary for him.
I thought this was my only chance to try something like this.
- That's so cool. - So I gave it a try.
- He didn't show his fear. - Seriously.
- Right. - If you had not done it,
this would've haunted you forever.
So if I had not done it,
you would've made fun of me forever.
I would've mentioned it...
- for over half a year. - Right.
- So you didn't want him to do that. - You would've mocked me...
- and called me a chicken. - You didn't want him to do that.
I knew he would mention that every time he saw me.
(He knew that Hyun Moo would call him a chicken.)
What's this? It keeps getting stuck. Okay.
- Just keep on pedaling. - Okay.
He's nervous.
Of course, it's scary.
I'm really sorry.
But could you check my gear one last time?
- He must double check it. - Why are you such a chicken?
- How could he not? - I was so scared.
- Ji Hyeon... - Just in case.
- Of course. - He's so cute.
My motto is safety first.
- That's really important. - You know,
- when I get on rollercoasters, - Yes.
I check the bar 300 times.
Hey, you might break it then.
- Everyone feels the same way. - Right.
- Yes. - You must double check it.
Why do you want to double check it?
Could you check my harness one more time?
- The harness looks perfect. - Please.
- Thank you. - Just don't cry, Ji Hyeon.
- You got this. - You got this, Ji Hyeon.
You can do this. Let's go.
- Let's go! - Go!
- Let's go. - Go.
- My gosh. - Why am I nervous for him?
- He must pedal hard. - Hold on.
- The first step must be tough. - Keep pedaling.
Oh, my. This is crazy.
(They slowly move forward.)
Both of them are handling it well.
(The two scaredy-cats move forward smoothly.)
They look great.
They're not so scared.
This is driving me crazy.
(This is driving me crazy.)
- Ji Hyeon. - This is driving me crazy. Come on.
(The scared brothers whine shortly after departing.)
- It's so windy! - Oh, the wind!
(A sudden gust of wind hits them.)
- Why is it so windy? - Do you see my shirt fluttering?
- It was very windy that day. - I can see that.
- Your shirt is fluttering. - Let's go.
- Okay, Ji Hyeon. Let's go together. - Please.
- Yes, please. - Let's go at the same pace.
This is indeed safe, right?
Why did they make such a thing?
(Why did they make such a thing?)
(I totally agree.)
(With a fundamental question,)
(he reaches the halfway point.)
Gosh, I'm tearing up.
(Gosh, I'm tearing up.)
I'm tearing up.
(Na Ra, same here.)
It's so scary.
When you're up there,
- you can't look down. - That's right.
It feels so strange. You can't even see the wire.
- I know. - It's scary.
- Ji Hyeon, the wind is the kick. - I know.
- Let's go at the same pace. - Okay.
- You go together when it's scary. - That's right.
My goodness.
(He gets back on the bicycle again as he lets out a big sigh.)
- Ji Hyeon, shall we go? - Okay. Let's go.
Let's go. Ji Hyeon, let's do this.
- Moo Do Ra Ji, let's go! - Moo Do Ra Ji, let's go.
Let's go.
Ma'am, I'm really sorry,
but would you check my safety gear once more?
Hey, you punk!
- Ma'am, I'm really sorry... - Hold on.
- His safety gear! - They were supposed to go together!
Then he went, "Hold on."
- What was that? - I had to be certain.
- Ji Hyeon. - You always go, "I'm sorry, but..."
Ji Hyeon.
I had to be certain.
Na Ra, that was your reaction. I seriously had no idea.
You should've asked her to check Na Ra's safety gear as well.
- I know. - Na Ra was off,
but you asked the staff to check your safety gear.
- "Please check my safety gear." - Why did you do that?
It was the first day we met.
- And Ji Hyeon disappointed me. - Na Ra was off.
- He disappointed you. - That's right.
- I mean, Na Ra... - You went, "Hey, you punk!"
I can tell that you guys are close.
To be honest, I didn't even think about Na Ra.
That's right.
(Am I safe? What should I do?)
Seriously.
(My safety comes first.)
(I was too scared.)
Ma'am, I'm really sorry...
(At an unexpected moment, he faces...)
(a sudden betrayal.)
Hey, you punk!
Mom!
He is looking for his mom. It must be really scary.
(The desperate cry of the betrayed man)
- It's secure. - Okay.
Everything is the same.
- I didn't touch anything. - Okay.
- You're fine. - He got his safety gear checked.
- Safety first. - Ji Hyeon isn't crying, is he?
(Is Ji Hyeon okay?)
(After securing his safety, he finally sets off.)
(Groaning)
(Teary)
Mom.
I think he is crying.
- He is crying indeed. - I teared up.
- You teared up, right? - Yes.
(Just let us...)
(run on the ground.)
Look down!
My goodness.
(Pedaling with his eyes squeezed shut)
Well done.
(A tearful ending)
- It's so scary. - I hate it so much. I hate it.
- Activities like this... - Did you do a good job?
- give you good memories. - How cool! They're so cool!
- Did you cry? - Na Ra cried.
No, I didn't cry.
- You cried. - You teared up.
(Staggering)
- You get scared so easily. - Just in case...
- You didn't wet your pants, right? - I didn't wet my pants.
I apologize to the owners who offer services...
for activities such as bungee jumping,
but I honestly don't see the point of them.
People say that danger makes them thrilling.
Why would they do such a thing?
- Ji Hyeon doesn't get it. - He means his words.
His eyebrows are raised.
Thanks to Ji Hyeon, I became less nervous.
- Really? - Yes.
Na Ra overcame his fear.
We overcame our fear.
(Together, the cowardly brothers overcame their fear.)
- Lean back. - Is there another activity?
- Okay. - He has no fear.
- Dowoon! - Okay.
Keep your back and shoulders on the floor.
(Moo Do Ra Ji moves on to enjoy the Giant Slide.)
Put it between your knees.
- Look down. - Please shout "Moo Do Ra Ji."
(The first person to go, Dowoon)
- Moo Do Ra Ji. - One, two...
(Shouting)
(Sluggish)
Dowoon doesn't hesitate.
(He goes down without energy or hesitation.)
- Is it long? - It's long and fast.
Yes, it's fast.
- It looks so fun. - It looks fun.
He'll probably do the bungee jump with the same facial expression.
(Grinning)
- Please come to the front. - Okay.
(The next one is Na Ra.)
- Step with your right foot. - Shouldn't you put on some pants?
(Joking)
Na Ra, are you in your underwear?
Yes.
Let's go. In 1, 2.
(Surprised laughter)
It's fast.
Let's go. In 1, 2.
(Surprised laughter)
(Laughing)
(Screaming)
What a laughter. My goodness.
He sounds like a crow.
So that was my reaction.
(Oh, my!)
Isn't this one nice?
- I feel dizzy. - This one is nice.
(I felt fine.)
I'm curious about Ji Hyeon's reaction.
Keep your back and shoulders on the floor.
- Oh, my. It's a bit short! - Good.
(It's a bit short!)
What are you unhappy about?
(Full of worries)
- I couldn't stretch my legs. - Right.
- Okay. - I thought it might be bad.
- Right. - I thought the sled might be short.
- Then you might stop. - Yes.
You need to let the staff know that you're vigilant...
- That's right. - and that you feel discomfort.
- You need to do that. - But if you give them a hard time,
they might mess up your gear.
So you make it sound like it's your fault.
- "Is it tight because of me?" - That's right.
- That's exactly right. - Right?
Safety comes first.
How many thoughts do you have before you go down a slide?
- Countless thoughts. - Seriously.
You check your safety without annoying the staff.
- Right. You don't annoy the staff. - No.
Ji Hyeon, don't be scared.
The blood vessels in my hands will burst.
- Let's go. - Don't be ridiculous.
- In 1, 2. Maintain your position. - Okay.
Ji Hyeon!
(Shouting)
You look exactly like the face on the T-shirt right now.
(You're lying.)
(Crying)
- You look the same! - You're right.
Hey, Ji Hyeon!
- You look the same. - Ji Hyeon.
The illustration lacks teeth, but it looks the same.
- How cool. - I look the same!
(He admits it.)
(Fascinated)
I got chills. Hyun Moo drew a future event.
- You keep making that face. - He is like Nostradamus.
- You keep making that face. - I drew him well.
Seriously, Hyun Moo.
(He is Moostradamus.)
- I see the resemblance. - Hyun Moo, you have sharp eyes.
(Prophet Moostradamus)
(He reaches the bottom looking like the T-shirt.)
(Crying)
(The man who values safety, Ji Hyeon collapses on the floor.)
It was pretty high, right?
- It was pretty high. - That's right.
Sky Cycle is scarier.
This one... Sky Cycle is scarier.
- This one is less scary. - His face is pale.
(Pale)
Keep your shoulders on the floor as much as you can.
- You'll go in this position. - Gosh, it's scary.
- Don't lean forward as you go down. - The slide was pretty steep.
- I see. - Maintain this position.
Hold on.
(My goodness. Hold on.)
- Let's go. In 1, 2, 3. - Hold on. You little...
Wait.
Wait. Why did you swear?
I swore at myself.
You swore at yourself.
- I swore at myself. - My goodness.
- "Why did I suggest this activity?" - You swore at your cowardly self.
That's right. I swore at myself since I suggested this activity.
- You swore at yourself. - Of course.
The person who suggests the ride always gets the most scared.
There was a sudden drop.
(That's me.)
That's me.
(Screaming)
(Laughing)
(Groaning)
(My goodness)
- It's fun. - It's no joke.
Seriously.
We had so much fun.
- We had so much fun. - How nice.
Seriously, it was fun.
Hold on.
I see a cafe.
- They must have iced Americano. - Of course.
- Isn't your mouth dry? - That's right.
My mouth is dry.
- It's dry, right? - Yes.
You don't have to eat anything.
Let's go.
Did you eat again?
I ate something warm since my body was cold.
(They go to a cafe to moisten their dry mouths.)
- It's cheese. - It looks good.
- Yes. - It's tasty.
- It's sausage. - You were eating...
after walking, running, and enjoying activities.
It was tasty.
Despite working out, I feel like I've gained weight.
It feels strange.
(This is the Fun Run.)
- Let's go. - I feel like I'm watching...
- high school boys hang out. - I know.
All right.
Ji Hyeon's getup suited him so well.
I haven't seen a conehead in a while.
- It's a lifestyle shop. - My goodness.
(Oh, my!)
How cute. If there are 4, it'll be nice to get 1 each.
- A whale each. - This is the whale run.
- That's right. - So we should get one each.
(Moo Do Ra Ji enjoyed the area around the observatory.)
What? They're still at the observatory.
Gosh, it's cold.
Hyun Moo, why is this place so windy?
- Every time we visited a place, - It's so cold.
- our sweat cooled down. - That's right.
- You know that we need to run. - Yes, of course.
- Let's run to keep ourselves warm. - Okay.
- Let's go. - The sun will rise.
- Okay. Run. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's do this.
(What remains of the whale run is the whale's belly.)
All right.
- It's an uphill. - An uphill.
- An uphill. - Is he wearing a blanket?
- Hyun Moo felt cold, - A blanket?
so he bought a blanket at a convenience store.
I've never seen anyone buy a blanket during a run.
- It means he didn't run much. - I didn't run much.
- He mostly walked. - I didn't sweat at all.
Wait.
Your body gets hot when you run.
My body didn't get hot at all.
I was so sad.
Buying a blanket during a run...
(The side effect of the Fun Run)
There weren't more, so I just got one for myself.
- You really are the president. - There was only one.
The blanket looks like a bib.
He looks like someone who ran away during a personal color analysis.
(He looks like someone who ran away during a personal color analysis.)
"I'll go and find my personal colors!"
(Let's go!)
- A downhill. - Once we go down, we'll be done.
- We're nearly there. - Really?
The route ahead of us.
The highlight of the whale run was the last part.
You should never go uphill for that part.
You should go downhill.
That way, you feel the cool wind from the sea...
and wrap up the entire run on a positive note.
I put the most amount of thought into the beautiful route.
(The end is near.)
(Trudging)
- Dowoon, are you okay? - Of course.
- You're walking. - Okay.
Dowoon, are you okay?
- Dowoon, are you okay? - That's it.
- Let's go. - You still have it.
Let's do this.
- Just run for a while longer. - You still have it.
I'm good at running downhill.
It's nice.
I can keep my pace when I run downhill.
- Hey! - Hey!
(Speeding)
- You're fast. - Hey!
- Hey! - Hey!
- It's a downhill. - Downhills excite me so much.
- Look. He is running fast. - He is excited.
(Hyun Moo puts a distance between him and other members.)
Look at that speed.
When it comes to running downhill, I can challenge anyone.
Sean and Kian84, come at me.
I'm the fastest.
I don't run when there is a downhill.
I just slide down like a car without the brakes.
So when we ran downhill, I violated the speed rule...
of the Fun Run.
I should've taken care of the members,
but I tossed them aside because I was so excited.
I just ran at full speed.
(The remaining distance is about 1km.)
We're nearly there.
- Are we nearly there? - We're nearly there indeed.
I see the starting point.
We can't go further.
(We can actually see the ending point!)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
We're nearly there.
That part was the highlight.
- How cool. - It's so pretty.
- What a route. - It's a nice route.
- Watch your ankles. - Watch your knees.
- We really should be careful. - Watch your ankles.
(The road is very steep.)
Watch your ankles.
(Steep slope? I enjoy it.)
Wait. Did someone push you?
- You're just running down. - I don't think he can stop.
- Seriously. - I couldn't stop.
He couldn't stop.
(He forgot about the members a long time ago.)
I tossed them aside because I was so excited.
- You're good at running downhill. - I'm good at running downhill.
Isn't he running too fast?
When I checked the pace,
it was 4 minutes and 30 seconds per kilometer.
- Really? - That was my pace for a downhill.
(Chief Moo has no intention to stop.)
- Why is he going so fast? - You can barely see my feet.
- Like the puppy run's crosswalk. - Exactly.
I run so fast at the crosswalk during the puppy run.
The last spurt.
(He made the last spurt during the puppy run.)
It's a downhill.
I bet it feels good.
- We're going to the supermarket. - Yes.
Be careful.
We're nearly there.
(With Chief Moo as the lead,)
(they run as one toward the end.)
The Fun Run.
(He shook up the running scene with the Fun Run.)
(He founded the Fun Run Crew and went from 1 to 4.)
(He invited people who have the desire to run...)
(to the world of Fun Run.)
This will be a small beginning.
(A small, but meaningful beginning)
Let's go.
(Today's group run)
(At the end, the four members...)
(complete the whale run.)
- Did you complete the run? - Yes.
We completed the run.
Yes.
(Well done, Moo Do Ra Ji!)
You filmed a video of the moment you completed the run.
- Did you film Hyun Moo? - Yes.
How cool.
(Winking)
- Hey, we did it. - Thank you for your hard work.
The whale run is complete.
It's complete.
- Mission complete. - Mission complete.
It felt really good to complete the run.
Hello, we're back.
Hello.
- Okay. - Hello.
The sun set when we finished running 10km.
They began at 8am, but the sun set.
I charged it earlier.
- My goodness. - I bet you burned many calories.
- Let's go. - What's the record?
- We ran for 5 hours and 35 minutes. - Okay.
- It's a full marathon. - And...
Did you say 5 hours and 35 minutes?
It took longer than a full marathon.
- The total distance. - Okay.
The total distance we've traveled is 12.62km.
- Is it over 10km? - We went beyond our goal.
(My goodness)
- Everyone. - Yes?
Are you ready to see it?
- We're ready. - I'm curious.
Now, I'll show you...
- the route we've taken. - I'm so curious.
Gosh, this is insane.
I think this is insane.
- I'm so curious. - I know.
Now, I'll show you...
- the route we've taken. - I'm so curious.
- I'm so curious. - I know.
One, two,
three.
- The whale run! - My goodness.
Three.
(The route they've sketched through GPS)
- The whale run! - My goodness.
We began here.
- You're right. - It's a whale, right?
My goodness.
(Eodal Intersection, lighthouse, observatory, community center)
We started at the intersection...
- and visited a lighthouse. - That's right.
Then we outlined the whale's spout.
(Observatory)
- The mouth looks legit. - It does, right?
Then we outlined the fin.
(Fun Run Crew)
Then we came back here.
(Eodal Intersection)
- Does it look good? - Yes.
- It looks pretty. - I know.
Doesn't it look good?
It really gave me a sense of accomplishment.
- It was a really nice run. - It was.
- It really is a whale. - It's a whale.
No way.
I'll show you mine.
Ta-da.
- I have it too. - The whale run.
- It's prettier than mine. - Here.
Look at this. This is the real deal.
(Two whales at the Gangwon Province)
- We ran really well. - I know.
- This is insane. - This is incredible.
It gave me a sense of accomplishment.
It gave me a big sense of accomplishment.
It was fun, and the route was pretty.
A whale with a big mouth...
was spouting water.
Its tail in the shape of an upside-down heart...
was attached at the end.
It was a very cute whale.
When I saw the shape,
I thought, "So this is how you complete the route."
It was fascinating.
"This is how you feel a sense of accomplishment..."
"by completing a run."
What I imagined in my head came true.
Realizing that...
made me so happy.
It was the perfect picture of what I had imagined.
(Highly satisfied with the completed whale shape)
Now, the average pace...
Do you want to see it first?
Don't share this information.
They'll lose their spirits.
- We don't know much. - That's right.
We don't know what's considered a good pace.
It was 26 minutes per kilometer.
- Did you say 26 minutes? - Per kilometer?
- Yes. - Twenty-six minutes!
That's like being stuck in heavy traffic on Gangbyeonbuk-ro.
- On Christmas Eve. - That's right.
- During rain and snow. - That's right.
We were slower than a worm.
- But it was the Fun Run. - Exactly.
- It was fun. - Exactly.
- That's right. - They're rationalizing the result.
- They're so good at rationalizing. - Is the pace so important?
- It isn't important. - It isn't important.
- It's better than not running. - Exactly.
- You got a workout today. - Yes, I did.
Toward the end, we ran at full speed.
- That's right. - Toward the end, I was like Sean.
I couldn't see my own feet.
I thought you had become Sean.
- Right? - Yes.
- I was so surprised at myself. - I know.
- I ran so fast. - I know. I was so surprised.
You were suddenly very far from us.
I ran the fastest toward the end during the last Fun Run.
I'm good toward the end.
- I give the last spurt. - I see.
- You make it fun at the end. - I make it fun at the end.
(I'll give you that.)
Be honest.
Do you want to eat or get warmed up?
- I want to get warmed up. - You want to get warmed up.
- Same here. - You want to get warmed up.
- I'm good with anything. Yes. - You want to get warmed up.
- I want to get warmed up. - Okay.
- Then you should get warmed up. - Can't you eat while you do that?
- It's because they ate a lot. - That's right.
- Right? - I was full.
- He was full. - Yes.
I expected as much and found the perfect spot...
for getting warmed up.
Let's go there right away.
- What? - What is it?
All right.
- You guys are babies. - It's so nice.
- It's so nice. - What is that place?
It's the lodging I've booked.
It must be a resort...
- with an outside bath. - Yes.
This is the last event of today's Fun Run.
(This is the last event of today's Fun Run.)
- Is it great? - It's great.
- It's great, right? - It's really great.
My Fun Run is serious about aftercare.
That way, the fun part becomes complete.
Fun Run always has an after-run service.
It always has an after-run service.
Last time, you got a massage.
That's right.
(When he did it alone, he got a massage...)
(to remove the toxins from running.)
We run for the after-run service.
To commemorate our Fun Run at the East Sea,
we can enjoy the view of the East Sea.
- How nice. - Isn't it unbelievable?
You get the full view of the sea when you sit down.
- This is incredible. - My goodness.
- You can hear the waves. - Of course.
That sounds amazing.
We can wrap up by enjoying the view of the sea.
I'm becoming drowsy.
- He is falling asleep. - Yes. It feels nice.
- He is drowsy. - Seriously.
- His eyes are half-closed. - Yes.
It was so nice.
- We made good memories. - Yes.
You completed the run.
There's a greater sense of achievement.
Imagine being like that after giving up in the middle.
- That would feel bad. - Right.
- That would feel bad. - That would feel bad.
(How was the 1st Fun Run?)
I thought this experience was only possible through the Fun Run.
As I was with the men, it reminded me of my army days.
We did so many things that day.
We naturally set our own roles.
I'm excited for the next Fun Run.
I'll be running a lot up until that time.
Gosh.
If there's a second Fun Run,
I want to be a part of it.
- Ji Hyeon must be in. - Gosh, Ji Hyeon!
He must come.
- What about you, Na Ra? - Give me a role.
Also,
I think we should set certain rules for the Fun Run.
- Let's listen to him. - Rules?
We shouldn't go to a cafe more than twice.
Right.
We shouldn't go to a restaurant more than three times.
If there's no rule,
I feel like it will become the Pig Run.
How can you call it the Pig Run?
Should I make it the shape of a pig next time?
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- I'll make a course. - With the pig's tail.
Right. I'll include the pig's tail.
The Jeju Island Black Pig Run.
- There are many parasitic cones. - Right?
We'll be there to support them from a distance.
We should visit a really good black pork place.
- There's a good place I know of. - Right. Let's do that.
Are you two going to go off topic?
As you mentioned black pork,
I was sharing about a good black pork place.
I think we should have those rules.
- I can accept those conditions. - Right?
Ji Hyeon seems like the perfect member.
It was great.
If I didn't invite them to the East Sea,
they would never have a chance to visit.
They were Gen MZers,
but they didn't know the Gen MZ spots.
They were pitiful Gen MZers who didn't know they were Gen MZers.
- I was the one to bring them out. - Right.
I want to give myself endless praise.
I did a great job.
I will never run again in my life.
- Gosh! - You won't run at all?
It wasn't my thing.
- He's honest. That's great. - He's honest.
That makes him a Gen MZer.
My Moo Do Ra Ji members!
I still had a lot of fun.
He's talking like someone who will never see us again!
- Seriously? - Hold on.
It's not just Moo Do Ra Ji.
It feels like he's done with I Live Alone.
- But... - Is that why he didn't come?
You don't have to run. You can be on the show.
(There's a reason for his absence?)
Should it be the Moo Ra Ji?
"Moo Ra Ji."
- "Moo Ra Ji." - It sounds like a loach.
I still had a lot of fun.
It was really meaningful to be a part of the first Fun Run.
- He already drew the line. - He has broken away from us.
I feel bad for not being able to carry on,
but as all of you were with me for this first run,
I believe it will end as a beautiful challenge.
- He's totally signing off. - It was an honor.
- "It was an honor." - "It was an honor."
This feels great.
Are you going to post it on Instagram?
I must.
"Moo Ra Ji."
The Moo Ra Ji that was the Moo Do Ra Ji.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
We're looking for members for the second Fun Run!
(We're looking for members for the 2nd Fun Run!)
I admit that Kian84...
- started a running boom. - Right.
But those who can't set records like Kian84...
find it hard to make an attempt.
- There are many shy runners. - Right.
- The Fun Run is for those people. - Right.
Without feeling left out.
The PR Team member.
Am I the team leader of the PR Team?
- Right. - Okay.
Personally, I wish to see Hyun Moo run with all his might.
- He did that on the way down. - Right.
(Smirking)
- Mr. Bae Na Ra? Leave the group. - A set distance.
- Leave if you're going to say that. - Na Ra is in danger.
- Na Ra! - That was harsh.
- The Moo Ji Run. - He seemed to be a great runner.
- The Moo Ji Run. - It's going to be the Moo Ji Run.
- He told him to leave. - They're breaking up now.
Moo and Ji.
"Moo Ji."
Can I be in my underwear again?
Be in your actual underwear next time.
(Joking)
To make it realistic?
- Wear briefs. - Go with briefs.
(He's desperate enough to be in his underwear.)
The Underwear Run?
"The Underwear Run!"
It's the Underwear Run! Gosh!
"The Underwear Run?"
The Underwear Run in Myeong-dong.
- The Underwear Run. - Right. The Underwear Run.
Gather crew members for the Underwear Run.
(It's the 1st Underwear Run!)
- That doesn't sound bad. - Gather people for the first run.
- Right. - Run an underwear-shaped course.
Let's go with the Underwear Run.
- Gosh! - That sounds like a lot of fun.
- The first Underwear Run. - I'll join if you're in it.
You should be that determined!
- Women wear underwear as well. - Right.
- Let's go with the Underwear Run. - I also...
- ran a lot when I was young. - In the middle of the city.
We're gathering crew members for the first Underwear Run!
(Fun Run crew, Moo Ra Ji)
(Fun Run crew, Moo Ji)
(Na Ra will be off for the Underwear Run.)
(I Live Alone)
(Bread Garde)
Fente!
- Fente! - What is this?
- Marche-fente. - Fencing?
Did he get a role of a fencer?
Fente!
This is the fencing center.
My teacher in high school...
said that fencing and horseback riding...
were good for actors.
That was when I first learned fencing and horseback riding.
COVID-19 struck around that time.
That was why I couldn't carry on after a few classes.
I wanted to learn it again when I had the time to.
So it has been three months since I started fencing.
(Points are earned by hitting the opponent with the sword.)
It's an amazing sport.
It feels great to see something new with fencing.
- It's a great workout. - Right.
It makes you sweat buckets.
(Bum June relaxedly enjoyed his bread.)
So you're working out to be able to eat bread.
You're right.
Make sure to have the right form.
I'll point it out right away if it's off.
En garde.
(Glaring)
One.
(They warm up with the basic form of going up and down.)
Two.
One.
(Strengthening the lower body is the most important in fencing.)
(The fencing rookie of 3 months does his best.)
- It's here. - Six.
- Like this. - Sang Uk...
(It's similar to the training Oh Sang Uk did.)
He has legs of a horse.
- Two, four. - His legs are thin.
- Gosh. - Five.
- My legs are shaking already. - Nine.
Ten. Okay. Loosen up.
Go!
Small steps!
(Skipping)
I reduced my cardio workouts after fencing.
There's already a lot of cardio for fencing.
- It works me out so much. - Right.
It's tough.
Fencing is really tough.
- It's really tough. - It's a full-body workout.
I quit fencing right away.
- You tried fencing? - Fencing...
He has tried doing everything except for getting married.
There was a fencing boom...
- because of Oh Sang Uk. - Right.
I thought my thighs were about to rip apart.
- Right. - The sword isn't...
given at the start.
- At the start. - The sword isn't given.
- Why not? - It's just this.
- It's just this. - It's just this.
This is all you do at the start.
(Going back and forth)
- This is all you do. - It looks like a dance move.
It was so exhausting!
- For a month? - Isn't there a Fun Fencing group?
Stop!
- Funcing! - Funcing!
- You should start a group. - Stop with the groups!
- No! - Sign up for the first Funcing!
- Please stop! - That sounds great.
It will take ten hours to make one poke.
(Let's have fun with fencing as well.)
Fente!
- Push forward. - Fente!
Actors need great observation...
- and concentration. - It happens in a split second.
Right. In fencing,
you have to observe your opponent a lot...
and it requires a lot of concentration.
So it really helped me in that sense.
That's great.
(The traits of fencing help with his acting.)
We have exactly 6 today. It's perfect for a 3-on-3 match.
- Right. - You all know this, don't you?
It's always a 3-on-3 match for team matches in fencing.
Right.
Get ready for the match.
(He gets changed after warming up.)
He doesn't have any armpit hair.
(He doesn't have any armpit hair.)
(Embarrassed)
Did you get it shaved?
When I was the MC for "Inkigayo,"
my stylist said I had to get my armpits shaved...
as they show when I say, "Goodbye, everyone!"
"Goodbye, everyone?"
(Goodbye, everyone!)
(His armpits showed whenever he said goodbye.)
That was why I decided to try waxing for the first time.
I went to a waxing place after looking it up.
I went to a waxing place...
- that many celebrities went to. - Right.
I saw Hyun Moo's photo on the wall.
It's like he's a restaurant model.
There are photos of him whenever it's about hair.
Did you get all the other parts waxed except for this part?
I wax all the other parts except for here.
Why do you leave this part?
- It's his trademark. - It's my trademark.
- Like the black bear. - To look sexy.
Right.
I didn't want to know, but I happened to ask about it.
(The warmups are over!)
(Sliding open)
(Fully dressed in the fencing suit)
He seems like an athlete!
(He takes care of his sword as well.)
Everyone wants to use the restroom.
Let's make it a bet for the team match.
Let's make it a bet.
As we're hungry, the losers will buy toast.
- Let's go. - Sounds good.
The losing team will pay.
What is the name of this team?
Bbangdol?
- Bbangdol. - We'll go with Bbangdol.
- You are Bbangdol. - Bbangdol.
- We'll call ourselves Bbangsoon. - Bbangdol?
- Bbangdol and Bbangsoon. - One, two, three, bread!
- One, two, three, let's go! - Let's go!
All right.
You must give everything you have for bread.
Right. I must.
You should be here.
(Team Bbangdol versus Team Bbangsoon)
- Min Jae is up first. - Right.
Come out, Seong Beom. It's Min Jae and Seong Beom.
Let's go, Min Jae!
(The line connected to the score machine is attached.)
Don't feel nervous. Just make your attack.
- You should watch carefully. - Right.
- Let's go! - His eyes changed.
Let's go!
(They get ready for the match after wearing the mask.)
The team match will be a 3-on-3 match with 9 rounds.
The 1st team to reach 45 points will take the win.
(Team Bbangdol versus Team Bbangsoon)
(It feels like a national team match.)
It feels tense.
- Let's go! - It's a team match.
It's a match for toast.
The losing team must pay no matter what.
(Bum June is having a 3-on-3 fencing match.)
Pret?
("Pret" means, "Get ready.")
Allez!
("Allez" means, "Go.")
It's okay!
(If the opponent's sword strikes the body,)
(the opponent scores.)
(Screaming)
- It's okay! - Fight until the end!
There you go!
(Screaming)
He has great reactions.
It kept going back and forth.
We changed turns every five points.
- Every five points. - Right.
That must be tough.
- So the points are accumulated. - Right.
It's the last turn.
- The score is exciting. - Right.
The score is exciting. It's great.
(Bum June's team is taking the lead by just a few points.)
Just go for the point even if you get hit.
- The last turn must be tough. - Right.
The last turn gives you the most pressure in group matches.
Right.
You two are both left-handed.
- I can't lose this match. - I didn't teach you that.
(Worried)
I've never scored a point against a left-handed fencer.
- Really? - It's true.
- You've never scored a point? - Right.
Against a left-handed fencer.
I've never scored a point against a left-handed fencer.
He's left-handed.
(The last opponent happens to be left-handed.)
How much longer has he been fencing for?
He has fenced for around a year and eight months.
- Then... - Right.
- He's an expert. - That's a big difference.
We'll have to expect you to lose then.
It will be hard to beat a fencer with that much experience.
But Bum June is really quick.
- I think it will be a tough match. - It might be a tough match.
Okay.
We were a point apart.
My teammates got the score up to 40.
I couldn't lose all of them during my turn.
You can do it!
Let's get together first.
- It's the last turn. - Let's go!
- One, two, three, bread! - One, two, three, bread!
- One, two, three, let's go! - Let's go!
Gosh!
Please.
- That must be a lot of pressure. - Please.
- It's the most exciting turn. - Don't go easy on him.
Why does this feel so never-racking?
Pret?
Allez!
- You start by poking at each other. - Right.
(Feeling nervous)
- Okay! - Yes!
- They both got hit. - What?
(They both got hit.)
(Both teams score a point.)
- Nice. - Nice.
En garde. Pret?
(The match resumes.)
Allez!
- Yes! - What's wrong?
Okay!
- What? - He poked him!
I was faster.
He's really good!
He's great!
I think the opponent will feel nervous.
The opponent is feeling rushed.
- Let's be calm. - Be calm!
- Don't rush it. - Hey!
(I must maintain this flow.)
Pret?
I've never won a match up until this time.
I always felt intimidated and afraid.
But today,
I wanted to use the many things I learned.
I'll try to bring out my spirit.
- He has the spirit. - Right.
Right. It's a mind game.
I entered a competition when I was in seventh grade...
and I won the silver medal.
- What kind of competition? - Judo.
I won against the previous year's champion.
- The fun thing about sports... - You can't predict what is to come.
is that you can't predict what is to come.
You can never know what will happen in sports.
- Okay! - Yes!
- You did it! - Yes!
My gosh!
- Okay! - Yes!
It was my first time taking the lead,
- and I felt a rush of dopamine. - Okay. Just two more points.
Nice one.
You're losing a game you must never be losing.
- Right. - Go for it.
He's rushing himself.
Didn't he come back after a year and eight months?
The one who feels the most nervous right now...
is the one who was a fencer for a year and eight months.
Losing to someone with three months of experience...
is unforgivable.
"You got poked by a fencer with three months of experience?"
- "Gosh!" - "Gosh!"
"Just use a toothpick at home!"
He's afraid of these responses.
He's the one who feels a lot more stress.
- Right. - Bum June has nothing to lose.
- Right? - But he's actually a great fencer.
There are times when things go against you.
- Right. - That happens once in a while.
Let's go for it.
(The opponent feels flustered.)
What are you doing?
Does it make sense that you're not scoring at all?
- There's only one point left. - Right.
Gosh!
(Against the left-handed fencer he was afraid of)
- There's only one point left. - Right.
You must've felt so nervous.
(I have come this far.)
I was so desperate to win.
(Until the gold medal,)
(he has 1 point left.)
- There's one point left. - This feels so tense.
This is fun to watch.
Just go for the poke.
Pret? Allez!
(The match resumes with great tension.)
- Be calm. - Be calm.
He's coming.
(Feeling nervous)
Be ready.
He has great form.
(Were both of them...)
(poked at the same time?)
(Who will take the point?)
(Bum June's team reaches 45 points.)
It's over!
(Seo Bum June did it!)
- It was a tough turn for you! - That was awesome!
(After a long match,)
Okay!
(Bum June's team takes the win.)
It's the gold medal!
(The same thrill of winning the gold medal)
(He can't hide his joy of victory.)
This is an emotional scene.
Seong Beom used to beat me all the time.
(Seong Beom used to beat me all the time.)
- It's my first time ever! - Right.
(It's my first time ever!)
Gosh!
- It was your first win? - Yes.
- After three months. - Right.
- As it was my first win, - Gosh.
I felt a rush of dopamine.
Okay!
The losers should now go and buy it.
Hold on! Time out!
(Time out!)
What is it now?
As it was my first win today,
- I will pay for it! - Okay!
(It will be my treat.)
- Nice! - He's making him feel worse.
- Gosh! - You're making him feel worse!
- If I were that guy... - Is he rubbing it in?
- He's a bit of a show-off. - I just...
- Right. - He's a bit of a show-off.
- He's a bit of a show-off. - What was that?
He would've already felt annoyed...
- from "Hold on!" - That's not it.
- He got too excited. - That guy...
already felt annoyed from "Hold on!"
It's even more annoying that he got everyone's attention like that.
- "Hold on!" - That's even more annoying.
"Please give me your attention!"
"Give your attention to the generous one."
"Look over here, losers!"
"Hey, losers!"
You're killing him twice.
Show-Off Seo.
"Give me your attention!"
- Gosh. - This is hilarious.
We were great during the first 30 minutes.
I feel so happy!
- Okay! - After losing all the time.
It's my first time!
He's rubbing it in until the end.
He's an icon of mockery.
Let's sit.
- Let's sit. - Right.
Gosh, I feel exhausted.
- Ta-da! - Yes!
- Nice! - Gosh!
He's serving it for them as well.
Here it is.
Take one each.
- Here you are. - Thank you.
- Is it a French toast? - Is it a French toast?
- It's the brioche. - The brioche?
I love the brioche.
- Gosh! - That must be delicious.
Even the losers should have that.
- You can't miss out on that. - You can't miss out on that.
- It was really good. - It looks delicious.
- The classic ones are the best. - Right.
Those are great.
I personally really like butter and eggs. Cheese as well.
The brioche is full of butter and eggs.
(It tastes even better after sweating a lot.)
- The sauce is insane. - Right.
- That was great. - That was great.
Nice one!
See you!
- Bye! - Bye!
(Bum June comes out after a good workout.)
He looks so happy today.
Are you running because you feel happy?
- I was in a hurry. - Oh, I see!
Monde! I'm back!
(He quickly runs back home.)
I'm back!
- Gosh! - That little baby.
He's so cute!
Who did that?
Who did that? Gosh, really?
Did you pee nicely as well?
I'll go and wash up.
(He heads to the kitchen after washing up.)
(Opening)
- You must eat now. - Right.
I got done with my appetizer.
You'll be eating in earnest.
(Up to three bowls of instant rice)
Gosh. It's instant rice.
Three? Someone must be coming.
- No. That must be for gimbap. - It takes three bowls?
You could use three bowls when making gimbap.
- That makes sense. - That's for making gimbap.
He really enjoyed his food.
Right. Just like that!
(An extraordinary big bite)
(He opens the fridge next.)
(Curious)
- What is he taking out? - What?
- The webfoot octopus. - Webfoot octopus!
They're in season.
I'll be making webfoot octopus fried rice...
and chive gimbap.
- I prepared the two. - Oh, my.
- You're making gimbap, right? - Yes.
- It's gimbap. - It is indeed gimbap.
(Pouring flour over the webfoot octopus)
It helps remove odor. And there's dirt...
- That's right. - in their suction cups.
That helps remove them better.
- Something like mud. - That's right.
It gets removed.
I really like stir-fried webfoot octopus.
But I don't like watery stir-fried webfoot octopus.
- You know what I mean, right? - Of course!
- It has to be thick. - When it becomes so watery...
- It has to be thick. - I know.
- With soju? - When you boil it,
- it gets too watery. - That's right.
Right. That's it.
- That's a technique. - That looks good.
You don't blanch it. You steam it.
I let it get cooked with the steam.
When it's watery and you add glass noodles,
- the soup is gone in a second. - That's right.
You add glass noodles to every kind of food.
- I mean, - Glass noodles?
- if you add glass noodles... - Where? Excuse me.
to webfoot stir-fried octopus,
- That sounds delicious. - Right. It sounds delicious.
- I love glass noodles. - I love it too.
(Goodness)
(Webfoot octopus steamed with soju)
You're making a dish...
- that can be done fast. - That's right.
- Gosh, it looks good. - It's well-cooked.
- That way, they become soft. - That's right.
Yes. Otherwise, it's too chewy.
It'd be delicious to dip that in sesame oil.
That's right.
- Now we're talking. - Right.
(Laughing)
- You portioned out butter? - That's right.
- How neat. - You're really good at homemaking.
You add butter too?
(Adding all sorts of vegetables after adding butter)
(Adding Cheongyang red pepper on top of it)
He's a good cook.
I can tell he cooks a lot.
I know. He's really good.
To make it even thicker, I added potato starch.
(Amazed)
(And adding chili oil)
That one is delicious.
- Oh, my gosh. - Why were you surprised?
- The aroma changes. - Yes. If you add chili oil,
it enhances the flavor.
- The aroma itself... - It's not easy...
- to make a smoky aroma there. - That's right.
(He knows his stuff.)
(Stevia)
That low-sugar sauce is guaranteed to be good.
(Stevia, allulose, low-sugar oyster sauce)
(He skillfully finished stir-fried webfoot octopus.)
He's really good.
He must cook often.
I can tell from his skills that he cooks a lot.
- His knife work... - He's faster than me.
(To three bowls of white rice,)
(add a round of sesame oil.)
(The rice for gimbap is ready.)
- No way! - He's really quick too.
Don't you check the recipe?
- No, I cook by instinct. - Normally?
- Those who cook often at home... - Of course.
- don't check the recipe. - By instinct. That's right.
- They go by feel. - It's more delicious...
if you cook by feel.
You see? Even when he makes gimbap...
He does it so prettily.
(Skillfully fixing the edge of the seaweed sheet with rice grains)
I can tell he makes gimbap a lot at home.
You don't use the rolling mat, do you?
- I just roll it. - Exactly.
- The mat... - It's done.
No way. It's so pretty.
(He finishes making 5 rolls of chive gimbap in no time.)
(Barking)
- Someone must be here. - Someone is here.
Someone is here.
Isn't it the guy who lost fencing to you?
He's so scary.
"Don't call for a timeout. Just get out."
(Rushing to the door)
(Screaming)
Who is it? Wait!
Who is it?
(Someone is visiting Bum June.)
Who is it? Wait!
- Who is it? - A member of TOMORROW X TOGETHER.
- You're right. - It's YEONJUN.
- I haven't seen him for a while. - Gosh, it's YEONJUN!
- He's really popular. - He's no joke.
- He's no joke. He's super popular. - TOMORROW X TOGETHER.
- I hosted "Inkigayo" with him. - Right! You hosted it with him.
- That's right. - Right.
(Bum June's close friend, YEONJUN)
You lost so much weight.
- Goodness. - You lost so much weight.
(They exchange greetings happily.)
Please wait.
- Play with Monde for a while. - Monde.
Monde.
Why did you lose so much weight?
- Right now, I... - For "KPop Demon Hunters..."
The artist of the movie thought of him...
- when he created Saja Boys. - That's right.
They thought of him for the character.
- Really? - That's right.
They created pink hair similar to his.
- That's right. - I think I've seen it.
My niece's dream is to see YEONJUN in real life.
- Really? - Yes.
I didn't know what you'd like, so I just bought whatever.
He must've gotten bread.
- I'm certain he got bread. - It must be bread.
Since you like bread,
I got you bread.
I'm not sure if you'll like these.
Hey, I love any kind of bread.
(That's right.)
I got various kinds.
YEONJUN loves eating too.
We like to go on an eating spree when we meet.
It'd be nice to have a friend like that.
I'm jealous. You don't gain weight either.
(Glancing)
You're using this well.
Of course. You gave it to me.
Gosh, this one. I'm so proud.
When I first moved there...
- You guys are so close. - Yes.
- A housewarming gift? - Yes, it was for a housewarming.
You guys are really close.
He's so sweet.
It doesn't feel like...
- I haven't seen you for a while. - I know.
(Lingering around after checking on the gift he gave him)
Gosh, it's been a while.
- By the way, YEONJUN, - Yes?
I put down that rug by myself with much difficulty...
- when I moved here. - Yes.
You did a good job.
But I'm going to remove it today.
- That's why you called him. - That's why you called him.
Goodness. A bolt out of the blue.
What's wrong with his face?
(Wait a minute.)
This?
- I really tried doing it myself. - You're removing the rug?
Yes.
I tried doing it myself...
That means you have to move everything before removing the rug.
- That's right. - You need to remove everything.
I put down that rug...
- for the vibe. - What?
- It's perfect for a dog to pee on. - Of course.
Right?
- Like a pee pad? - A pee pad!
It's a big pee pad.
- The thing is, puppies... - Is that so?
- That's right. - can't tell what's a pee pad...
- and a rug. - Of course, they're confused.
That's why when it peed, I removed each piece...
and cleaned it 1 by 1.
- I tried removing it myself, - You can't.
- but I could never. - Of course not.
So I was going to ask YEONJUN for help...
and cook him something nice.
When you live alone, it's really hard...
to move furniture when seasons change.
Removing them is really hard.
- I know. - You need to pack and move them.
Also, you need to lift the pieces underneath too.
That's right.
So then, let's give it a go.
(Taking off)
Hey.
I mean...
Okay.
Let's do it in earnest.
Gosh, this guy is cool.
(Let's do it in earnest.)
- I will... - First of all...
- Remove them all? - We can't move them at once.
- Let's put down the things on top. - Okay.
We need to remove all these.
It'll be easy if you remove the stuff first.
That's what I find the most tedious.
- Right? - Yes.
Then...
(Shall we remove the rug now?)
For the tiles here...
You can just remove it when you lift it.
Then it'd be doable. It'll be done in no time.
It's quite heavy.
- I feel like it'll be torn. - They're like dumbbells.
They're heavy.
I think it'll be heavy.
(Together, they're as heavy as dumbbells.)
Let's tilt the dresser on its side...
and remove the tiles underneath.
Then what should I do?
Hold on. Let's pull it a bit.
- In 1, 2, 3. - How?
How do I pull it?
How do I do it?
- Gosh. - Hold on.
- It must be heavy. - All my scripts are in there.
How do I pull it?
- I'll push this. - Okay.
Then you can remove the tiles.
- You know what I'm saying? - Okay.
One, two, three.
- That's it. - Nice!
They have great teamwork.
There's one on the inside too.
Right. But for that, you need to push this...
- That's right. - Oh, we can remove this soon.
- Gosh. - I got it.
- We'll be done with it soon. - I know.
(Cleaning up the rug tiles behind the dresser as well)
What do we do with this?
- First... Let me see. - You have to lift that too?
Yes, I placed them under the bed too.
- Even the bed? - How do you remove those?
Can't I remove them as is?
It wouldn't work.
You need more than two people.
- Gosh. - That's the issue.
- That's really heavy. - It's really heavy.
How about we push the bed sideways?
- The bed? - Yes. Let's not lift the bed.
After removing them, let's slide it back like the dresser.
- Okay. - Let's give it a try.
All right!
- One, two... - One, two, three.
(Pushing the bed, following Bum June's idea)
Pull it!
Gosh. Bum June, you have great arms!
(Using all his strength)
- Gosh. - What?
- It was really heavy. - Is he pulling it?
(It's not budging as if it's fixed on the floor.)
Why wouldn't it budge?
Hold on. We need another strategy.
Wouldn't it be better to remove the mattress first?
I think it'd be better if we remove the mattress first.
Is the mattress the problem?
- The mattress must be heavy. - That's right.
(They change the plan and go for the mattress first.)
You're right.
All right. One, two, three.
(Heave-ho)
- Let's go! - Okay.
We got it. Good job.
(Removing the mattress with a loud shout)
Then...
You must've prepared something really delicious.
Just you wait.
- That's it. It works. - This...
Wouldn't it be better to move it after lifting it?
Instead of pulling it.
- You should lift it... - It's better to lift it.
and remove the tiles.
One, two, three.
(They try lifting the frame just as YEONJUN suggested.)
(Grunting)
- You can't even lift it? - Wait. Why... Are they too old?
- Gosh, this is... Yes? - YEONJUN.
I'll hold it after we lift it together.
- Okay. - All right.
One, two, three.
(Let's give it another try. One, two, three.)
It wouldn't budge.
How come you have no strength?
I can even lift a bed bigger than that.
What?
You should lift weight instead of doing fencing.
(Getting hit)
You can't use your strength at all.
Shouldn't you pull the bed a bit and lift it?
It's because one side of the bed is stuck on the wall.
It would be better if it were a bit apart.
You can't get the angle.
- I know. - You couldn't think of that.
- You didn't use your brain? - No.
How could you say that?
Now that I'm seeing it, you guys are right.
(Even he himself is frustrated.)
Hold on.
Let's use our brains, Bum June.
Can't we remove them below the surface?
He's similar to you.
YEONJUN isn't using his brain too.
- Right. - I don't know...
Right? It doesn't seem too bad.
I think YEONJUN is smart.
- Me too. - Me too.
(A super generous standard for the K-pop star)
- He's really intelligent. - I think he's...
I wasn't saying anything much, but the two dug their own graves.
- No. - I didn't say anything.
I dug my own grave and covered it on my own.
I had a good first impression of him from the start.
You guys are trying so hard to survive.
- Look at that. Look at his muscles. - He's such a good friend.
- He's sensitive. - Right.
(I love YEONJUN.)
- Like this. - Yes.
- Wait. - Right? It's not bad, right?
- If you... - Right?
pull it from the gap...
- Let me try. - Gosh!
- He's so smart. - It's not bad, right?
You'd have been in big trouble if it had not been for YEONJUN.
He's really smart.
He's indeed shining YEONJUN.
(He's indeed shining YEONJUN.)
I think we can lift this. Let's give it another try.
- Let's give it another try. - This?
Yes, one, two, three.
(Giving it another try after gathering strength)
It works. It's working, Bum June.
Because there's a gap...
That's right. It's because of the gap.
I'll hold this, and...
- Should I remove them? - Yes.
(Quickly removing the tiles while Bum June is holding the bed)
That's it.
Yes!
Okay.
(Grunting)
Goodness.
Hurry!
I'll hold it with my body.
- You can put it down. - No.
I got it. It looks good now.
Bum June, you need to take care of those.
- Should I remove them? - You should do it.
- Remove your arms. - I'll put it down.
(Retreating the tiles by sacrificing themselves)
(Bum June...)
Put it down. Get out.
(Get out, YEONJUN.)
Just hurry up and clean up.
- You want me to clean up? - Yes.
You want me to clean up?
- Should I let go? - Let go and clean up.
- Should I clean up? - Gosh, that's seriously...
Hurry up and take them.
Hey. Hold on.
(The older one feels rushed upon seeing the younger one suffer.)
I don't have a vacuum cleaner. You should get out.
The vacuum cleaner is outside. Get out.
(The vacuum cleaner is in the living room.)
The vacuum cleaner is outside.
(The older one holds it even when the younger one left.)
I didn't know we had no sense of work.
I thought we did it fast in a really smart way.
(The younger one brought the vacuum cleaner with struggle.)
He brought the vacuum cleaner.
Okay. What do we do?
Bum June, hold on. I'll put it down here.
I'll just use my body.
(Tossing the vacuum cleaner he brought)
Go ahead.
(I should do it?)
Bum June, you do the wiping.
(He was handed the vacuum cleaner as though he was immersed.)
YEONJUN could be cleaning.
He learned to do fencing, that's why.
- You're right. - The epee.
You would've won if you had attacked like this.
- Like this. - That's right.
Get out.
(He's not so skilled, but he's warmhearted.)
I'll put it down.
(Sighing)
(Exhausted)
- Hey, hold on. - What?
- What? - My hand is stuck.
- No! - Hold on.
- You got it? - I got it.
(Sweating buckets after removing only a few tiles)
He's sweating so much.
Gosh.
It's nice.
(Flopping)
I didn't sweat as much when I went fencing earlier.
Monde, this isn't the right time.
(Monde is the only one full of energy.)
(Tired)
Let's just hurry up and get it done with.
- Okay. - It's easier said than done.
What do we do with the tiles on the inside?
- I... - Yes?
I'll go to this side and lift the other side.
You should remove the tiles quickly. What do you say?
He's only good at explaining things.
I'm only good at explaining things? You're right.
I should go to that side.
Hold on. All right.
One, two, three.
- We got it. - All right.
Wait.
(YEONJUN is trying to collect the tiles under the bed.)
Why don't you let it go and remove the tiles with me?
- What? - Let it go.
- Oh, like this? - Yes.
- Got it. - This isn't too bad.
Not bad, right? It's possible to use our bodies.
(Using their bodies, they collect all the tiles.)
Hold it.
I got it. We can let it go.
- What is it? - Did they get hurt?
(Shocked)
What was it?
A part of the frame fell.
(Suddenly, a part of the frame fell.)
It's okay, YEONJUN.
As long as we're not hurt.
You keep getting more work.
- I'll put it down for now. - Do we have space to get out?
Hold on.
- What do we do? - It's so tormenting.
You need to get out for now.
It's not that. This...
This part can't...
(Struggling)
What do we do?
(Throwing)
Darn it. This is so...
(Throwing away his stylish glasses due to the grueling labor)
- One second. - Bum June.
This is crazy.
(This time, they give it another try with YEONJUN's help.)
(Screaming)
(Dropping it on the top of his foot)
- Oh, my gosh! - It fell on the top of my foot.
Since you got rid of your couch, why don't you get rid of your bed too?
What are you guys doing?
(Panting)
Why wouldn't it work?
Monde, come and help us.
(Me?)
My leg... Bum June, let it go.
Bum June, I'll hold it with my legs. All right.
(Grunting)
(Getting the sweet break after giving up their knees)
(Why did I want to do this?)
I think that's more workout than fencing.
Stay.
That's it. That's right.
That's right. That's what I'm saying.
Let's just remove that. Don't use it.
- Watch your back. - One, two, three.
(Let's put it down now.)
How low will my underwear go?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- I'll take this. - No.
The dust...
I mean, the dust...
There's just so much dust.
(Using the vacuum machine like a lint roller)
Wipe it off.
(Sighing)
(Startled)
(YEONJUN, you're okay, right?)
- Shall we keep going? - Yes, let's do this. Hold on.
Yes, you should finish it off while you're at it.
This is...
- He lied down? - I'll push it.
One, two...
That's it. You need to push with your back against the wall.
They got it.
One, two, three.
We're almost done.
(Placing the mattress on the top)
Put the cushion there.
(After placing the cushion at the head of the bed)
(They're done with removing the rug.)
We're done.
Gosh, you worked so hard.
We're done!
We're done.
Oh, my. Monde.
- I'll make you a nice meal. - Sounds good.
Hold on.
I'll make it quick.
(Let's get it ready fast.)
- The knife-cut noodles. That one. - Yes.
- It's not made of tofu, is it? - No.
- It's made of flour. - Flour? I see.
(He cooks quickly as he's worried about his friend who's hungry.)
- Gosh, it looks good. - Gosh.
- The knife-cut noodles... - Cooking knife-cut noodles...
- It looks so good. - Gosh.
You can add thin noodles...
or udon noodles to stir-fried webfoot octopus.
But I thought the chewy texture of the knife-cut noodles...
would go so well with webfoot octopus.
That's why I added the knife-cut noodles.
The sauce is absorbed in the noodles so well.
Right. Because they're thin.
- Gosh, you made this? - Yes.
Hold on. I'll make it delicious.
You did so much.
I think webfoot octopus will go well with gimbap.
- Right? - Because it's mild.
You know it needs konjac noodles, right?
Since it's webfoot octopus.
We're adding flying fish roe.
(Crunchy flying fish roe)
Nice.
That's maesaengi tofu.
Gosh, he's a good cook.
YEONJUN likes noodles, and he likes spicy foods too.
(A table of Bum June's spicy stir-fried webfoot octopus)
Great job.
- Great job. - I'm hungry.
Bum June cooks properly.
He's really good.
- Gosh, this is crazy. - All right.
- On top of this... - This is crazy.
- This is crazy, Bum June. - Add one piece of webfoot octopus.
And then...
Then I'll add mayonnaise on top.
And then... You know it, right?
Load the ssam with the flying fish roe.
You must add flying fish roe.
- That's a must. - Yes.
- He knows how to eat. - This is good.
And put this on top.
Hyun Moo, he's no joke.
He is really no joke. He really knows his stuff.
(Munching)
- That's it. - Look at the way he eats.
- You must take a big bite. - That's right.
(Exclaiming)
Oh, my. Look at YEONJUN eat.
- He's eating with gusto. - Goodness.
- How can he eat so heartily? - He eats well.
How is it?
- It's crazy. - It's crazy? Is it good?
- It's good, right? - Yes.
Gosh.
You're good.
- It's delicious. - Yes.
(Taking another bite of webfoot octopus on top of gimbap)
(Amazed)
- I want to eat like that! - Adding webfoot octopus on top.
- My gosh! - That's right.
(Me too.)
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh.
Put the whole webfoot octopus on top.
(This time, it's a combination of tofu and webfoot octopus.)
- Gosh, this is amazing. - The tofu...
is very condensed.
- It's like cheese. - That's right.
- It's my first time seeing that. - It has the maesaengi aroma too.
Take a whole bite.
(Filling his mouth with tofu and webfoot octopus)
What do you think? This is it, right?
- It's crazy. - My gosh.
- You really like konjac noodles. - I love konjac noodles.
(Placing)
Eat up.
This is the tastiest out of what I've had recently.
- Really? - Yes.
- He says things nicely. - Right?
Then...
I'm happy that you're enjoying it.
Yes, eat a lot.
(Shall I eat in earnest?)
(Adding thinly sliced pork belly)
- Rolled thinly sliced pork belly. - Thinly sliced pork belly.
- Gosh, the smell! - Are you adding it?
That's right.
This way, it feels like a new dish.
- You're right. - Have it with webfoot octopus.
- This is driving me crazy. - Gosh.
The rolled, frozen thinly sliced pork belly.
This is webfoot octopus with pork belly.
(Starting the 2nd round with webfoot octopus and pork belly)
(The two inhale the food without getting tired.)
If I eat this, I can't have another meal.
- Gosh. They eat so well. - Nice.
- He eats so well. - I know.
Whenever we meet,
we order 3 or 4 rounds of food.
We keep ordering food.
When I eat with YEONJUN,
he's like my pacemaker.
We get along well that we even go for 5 to 6 rounds.
He keeps up with me. We get along well when we eat.
YEONJUN.
My belly is huge.
(My belly is huge.)
My belly is protruding too.
- How is that huge? - What exactly is protruding?
You call that huge?
- I can't tell. - Shall I stick it out?
Go ahead.
You want me to stick my belly out for real?
You are already.
Stick it out like this, and then it goes back.
I ate a lot.
- No, if you use the bathroom... - Look at this.
- That's him sticking his belly out? - Yes.
You stretch it out to make more space.
- I have something for you. - Do you want some coffee?
- You do? - Yes.
What is it?
(Expectant)
Remember the snack you asked me to get...
when I went to the US?
So, I...
(Delighted)
I got you the snack you like.
I've been really craving it.
Bum June, thank you so much. You're so thoughtful.
You got the exact things that I wanted.
- Really? - Yes.
- I'm glad. - Thank you so much.
I'm really glad.
I was really grateful.
If it had not been for YEONJUN,
I'd have never been able to clean up by myself.
I had such a happy day again.
And I was grateful.
(Having a dessert to wrap up the meal)
- He eats well. - Seriously.
He's sleeping for real?
- He slept for real. - He'd need that sleep.
I kept eating.
He had a blood sugar spike, so he fell asleep right away.
(Sound asleep)
(A Grueling, Sweaty Day)
(Next story)
I'm Kim Shin Young of "Hope Song at Noon."
(I'm Kim Shin Young of "Hope Song at Noon.")
(It's been 14 years since she's been working as a radio DJ.)
(Now, I'm like the employee.)
(As a semi-employee, she gets off work fast.)
(Bowing)
(My house, my world)
(I'm finally home.)
(Cutting hair as soon as she gets home)
(Gosh, that's refreshing.)
(Highly satisfied with cutting hair by herself)
(Cleaning the bathroom right after cutting her hair)
(You need to remove the door to call it proper cleaning.)
(Neat)
(Getting ready to wipe after wetting the customized rag)
(Scrubbing the inside of the toilet thoroughly)
(Cleaning both the bathroom and my body neatly)
(Homebodies are even busier at home.)
(Cleaning's done.)
(It's time to wash away fatigue with high-calorie foods.)
(Sucking)
(Pouring the whole tub of ice cream)
(Cracking)
(Adding the crushed potato chips)
(A perfect sweet-and-salty combination)
(Taking a big bite)
(A thrilling burst of filling her mouth after work)
(The ultimate reward after work, a late-night snack)
(My Home, My World)
(Joy with fiery eyes...)
(immersed in something?)
(This is a pet grooming school.)
(Joy's half exciting and half nerve-racking challenge)
(This all began...)
(from her serious contemplation about the future.)
(Efforts built up amid a busy schedule)
(The day the wig she's been making for two months gets done)
(I'm good at it now.)
(Unusual scissor work)
There are rules for everything.
(Flipping)
(The ultimate horse-riding stance)
(Staggering)
(Cutting off the tail as well)
(And one person who's been watching everything)
(It won't work, will it?)
(You will be disqualified.)
(No!)
(Will I be able to complete it within today?)
(Someone is welcoming exhausted Joy?)
(Who is it?)
(Haetnim, her parents' dog who's here for a daily study)
(Studying for a written test with Haetnim)
(My helpful memorization fairy)
(This is too hard.)
(Until the day she passes,)
(studying is the only way.)
(It is Not Easy At All)